If you want to know how to make this
super easy coconut frozen yogurt at home
in your Ninja Creamy, then [music] stay
tuned and I'll show you that it's just
incredibly simple to make.
[music]
I recorded this video a couple of days
ago, but I went off on a tangent with
it. So, I thought I'd refilm the start
because this is not the kind of recipe
that I would normally do. This isn't
kind of balanced in a traditional way.
This is more of an experimental frozen
yogurt. I've done this with kind of
gelato settings just to see or gelato
baselines just to see what the result
is. But this has turned out so nice I
thought I'd just refilm some of this
video again. So, what are you going to
need for this experimental coconut
frozen yogurt? You're going to need 296
g of Greek yogurt, the lower fat
version, so 2% fat or less. Skin milk
powder 37 gram, alulose 100 gram, and
coconut cream 327
g.
I used a coconut yogurt in this. So, we
got coconut flakes in there. By all
means, add some yourself. I think it
really does elevate this frozen yogurt a
lot by having those pieces of coconut in
there. So, this is delicious. Let's get
everything out weighed and let's get
going. Right, let's get everything
ready. Get it in the pan. And we're
going to try and make this as cold
processed as we can, but we might need
to heat it up just to get the alulos
dissolved properly. So, coconut cream.
Loads of different types of fat content
for co coconut cream. There doesn't seem
to be like a common level, but this one
is Man, I haven't got my glasses on. 18
g per 83 milliliters. So, gives you an
idea of what I'm working with. So, we're
going to go with 327 g of this. This is
balanced for a Ninja Creamy Deluxe. 750
g millilit size. So if you want to do a
standard ninja creami, you're going to
need to knock 1/3 of it out. Okay,
it's just shy of a whole can. I mean,
there's probably a tablespoon left in
there. Into that, we're going to add our
Greek yogurt. I've actually got one with
a high protein count. I mean, you don't
need to, but I just what I eat. Um, and
mine's got coconut in it. You don't need
to,
but why not? So 297 300 g. Now I balance
this with skim milk powder. I'm going to
use coconut milk powder.
I I'm interested to see the result. So
let's wing it with this one a little
bit. 37 g of our coconut milk powder.
Now obviously this has much higher fat
than our skim milk powder. So let's
going to put our recipe off balance.
Let's see if it turns out okay. Finally,
in goes our alos. 100 grams.
There's a lot of solids going on in
here. It's quite a thick base. This
likely wouldn't work for a standard
churn machine because it's just going to
be too thick. But by all means, give it
a try. Let me know in the comments if it
works out. But now, we are definitely
going to need to heat this up to blend
this down. Get that coconut milk powder
completely dissolved into our liquid, of
which there's not a huge amount. So,
let's get that warmed up. Not hu not
super high. Something like 40, 50
Celsius, something like that. And then
we'll bring it back. Man, this base is
super thick. Um, like I said at the
start of video, there's
I don't think there's much chance in a
standard CH machine getting through this
base. Way too thick. And if it could,
there's going to be no overrun. It It
won't produce enough air. So, this kind
of is
designed for this kind of machine. the
quez art freeze wand or whatever it was
called. That could probably cope with
this. You'd have to go slow with a drop
with the Ninja Creamy. Let's see.
There we go. Let's get that in the
freezer. It's going to have to stay in
there 24 hours to harden off. Again,
it's slightly higher fat content than
the balanced recipe. It's not really the
kind of recipe that we can balance
properly because it's a bit of a
makeshift recipe, but we'll talk about
that maybe in next week's video when I
go into a bit more detail into Patrick's
ice cream calculator. So, let's get this
in the freezer to completely harden off.
Probably going to do this on
Oh, let's let's just do this on normal
ice cream setting and see what happens.
Okay,
let's have a look. Oh, I kind of
expected that,
but that's okay. We can spin that. Let's
just go exactly the same.
How did this turn out now? All right,
let's get some dished up.
>> [music]
>> So, there we go. Coconut frozen yogurt.
I did start this video very differently
with the intention of using uh a
different ice cream calculator to show
you the balance, but this recipe was
really odd and I kind of went off on a
tangent. So, next week I will do a
designated video for that ice cream
calculator alone. But let's try this ice
cream. Frozen yogurt.
Really nice, tangy.
You can taste that yogurt in there. The
coconut. It's really nice, strong
flavor, but not overpoweringly strong.
Texture is excellent. Yes, I had to spin
this one twice, but this recipe is kind
of like totally off normal charts.
[music] More of an experiment really,
but it's it's worked.
So, really delicious. Very easy frozen
yogurt ice cream for the Ninja Creamy. I
hope you give this one a try. Thanks
very much for watching. Don't forget to
like and subscribe and I will see you
next week.